Guide to the Cornell University Library Academic Personnel Policy Committee records, 1971-2005.
Cornell University Library Academic Personnel Policy Committee records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Library Academic Personnel Policy Committee records, 1971-2005.
13-11-2173
Cornell University Library.Academic Personnel Policy Committee.
.8 cubic ft.
Manuscripts
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes and other records of the committee including records of H. Thomas Hickerson, Philip Dankert and Caroline Spicer.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes and other records of the committee including records of H. Thomas Hickerson, Philip Dankert, and Caroline Spicer.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University Library.; Hickerson, H. Thomas.; Spicer, Caroline.; Cornell University.Library--Administration.
Subjects:
Librarians--New York (State)--Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Academic Personnel Policies, 1974 - July 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Academic Personnel Policy: Grievance Procedure, 1974, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Committee Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Academic Assembly Minutes, July 1981 - April 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Background Material, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee Meeting, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Academic Personnel Policy Search Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Economic Status material, 1971-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Academic Personal Policy Committee: Miscellaneous Papers, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Review and Grievance: Drafts and Related Documents, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Governing Documents, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Academic Personal Policy Committee: Incomplete Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Academic Personnel Policy, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Standing Committee on Academic Personnel Policy, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- CUL: Committee on Academic Personnel Policy, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- CUL: Committee on Academic Personnel Policy, 1970's (Box 1, Folder 23)
- CUL: Committee on Academic Personnel Policy, 1970's (Box 1, Folder 24)
- CUL: Committee on Academic Personnel Policy - Procedure 13, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- CUL: Committee on Academic Personnel Policy, 1970's (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Evaluation Ad-Hoc Committee, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee, 1974-1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Academic Appointment Manual, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Other Procedures and Bylaws, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Membership in CU Faculty, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Committees and boards, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Unfinished business, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Procedure 13, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Personnel Policy Committee, 1982-1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Personnel Policies, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence; Other business, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Personnel Policy Committee, 1983-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- APPR Search Committee Project, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- APPC Review Board Question, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- APPC Memos, etc, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- APPC Principal Investigation Policy, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- APPC Procedure 13, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- APPC Minutes, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Promotion, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- APPC Promotion Orientation, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Bylaws (Box 2, Folder 26)
- CU Consulting Policies for Librarians, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- APPC Meeting Notes, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- APPC Meeting Notes, April 2005 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- APPC Meeting Notes, April - May 2005 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- APPC Minutes, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Non-Tenure Track, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- APPC Records, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 33)